张穿着深色衣服，在夜间偷偷溜出房间。
Zhang, dressed in dark clothing, stealthily leaves a room at night.
雪春走下楼梯，走进月光下的传统花园。
Xuechun descends stairs and walks into the moonlit traditional garden.
雪春身着传统服饰，穿过月光下的花园。
Xuechun walks through the moonlit garden.
雪春夜间若有所思地站在花园小桥旁。
Xuechun stands thoughtfully by the small garden bridge at night.
雪春从屋里穿过拱门，步入月光下的花园。
Xuechun steps from the house into the moonlit garden through an archway.
雪春站在门口，四处张望，然后用手比划。
Xuechun stands in the doorway, looking around, then gestures with hands.
雪春关上门，转身扫视着黑暗的花园。
Xuechun closes the door, then turns and scans the dark garden surroundings.
雪春独自站在黑暗的花园中，缓慢转身。
Xuechun stands alone in the dark garden, turning slowly.
雪春走向张，张跪着遮住自己的脸。
Xuechun walks towards Zhang, who kneels and covers his face.
雪春看着张慢慢露出脸。
Xuechun looks at Zhang as he slowly reveals his face.
雪春为张打开了华丽的花园门。
Xuechun opens the ornate garden door for Zhang.
张用刀刺向雪春。
Zhang stabs Xuechun with a knife.
张培赞抬头微笑。
Zhang Peizan looks up and smiles.